[
    {"question": "6 + 5", "answer": "11"},
    {"question": "6 + 6", "answer": "12"},
    {"question": "6 + 7", "answer": "13"},
    {"question": "6 + 8", "answer": "14"},
    {"question": "6 + 9", "answer": "15"},    
    {"question": "7 + 5", "answer": "12"},
    {"question": "7 + 6", "answer": "13"},
    {"question": "7 + 7", "answer": "14"},
    {"question": "7 + 8", "answer": "15"},
    {"question": "7 + 9", "answer": "16"},
    {"question": "8 + 5", "answer": "13"},
    {"question": "8 + 6", "answer": "14"},
    {"question": "8 + 7", "answer": "15"},
    {"question": "8 + 8", "answer": "16"},
    {"question": "8 + 9", "answer": "17"},
    {"question": "9 + 5", "answer": "14"},
    {"question": "9 + 6", "answer": "15"},
    {"question": "9 + 7", "answer": "16"},
    {"question": "9 + 8", "answer": "17"},
    {"question": "9 + 9", "answer": "18"},
    {"question": "12 - 3", "answer": "9"},  
    {"question": "12 - 4", "answer": "8"},  
    {"question": "12 - 5", "answer": "7"},  
    {"question": "12 - 6", "answer": "6"},  
    {"question": "12 - 7", "answer": "5"},  
    {"question": "12 - 8", "answer": "4"},
    {"question": "13 - 4", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "13 - 5", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "13 - 6", "answer": "7"},  
    {"question": "13 - 7", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "13 - 8", "answer": "5"},
    {"question": "13 - 9", "answer": "4"},
    {"question": "14 - 5", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "14 - 6", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "14 - 7", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "14 - 8", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "14 - 9", "answer": "5"},
    {"question": "15 - 6", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "15 - 7", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "15 - 8", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "15 - 9", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "16 - 7", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "16 - 8", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "16 - 9", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "17 - 8", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "17 - 9", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "18 - 9", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "6 \\times 3", "answer": "18"},
    {"question": "6 \\times 4", "answer": "24"},
    {"question": "6 \\times 5", "answer": "30"},
    {"question": "6 \\times 6", "answer": "36"},
    {"question": "6 \\times 7", "answer": "42"},
    {"question": "6 \\times 8", "answer": "48"},
    {"question": "6 \\times 9", "answer": "54"},
    {"question": "7 \\times 3", "answer": "21"},
    {"question": "7 \\times 4", "answer": "28"},
    {"question": "7 \\times 5", "answer": "35"},
    {"question": "7 \\times 6", "answer": "42"},
    {"question": "7 \\times 7", "answer": "49"},
    {"question": "7 \\times 8", "answer": "56"},
    {"question": "7 \\times 9", "answer": "63"},
    {"question": "8 \\times 3", "answer": "24"},
    {"question": "8 \\times 4", "answer": "32"},
    {"question": "8 \\times 5", "answer": "40"},
    {"question": "8 \\times 6", "answer": "48"},
    {"question": "8 \\times 7", "answer": "56"},
    {"question": "8 \\times 8", "answer": "64"},
    {"question": "8 \\times 9", "answer": "72"},
    {"question": "9 \\times 3", "answer": "27"},
    {"question": "9 \\times 4", "answer": "36"},
    {"question": "9 \\times 5", "answer": "45"},
    {"question": "9 \\times 6", "answer": "54"},
    {"question": "9 \\times 7", "answer": "63"},
    {"question": "9 \\times 8", "answer": "72"},
    {"question": "9 \\times 9", "answer": "81"},
    {"question": "18 \\div 3", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "21 \\div 3", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "24 \\div 3", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "27 \\div 3", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "24 \\div 4", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "28 \\div 4", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "32 \\div 4", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "36 \\div 4", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "30 \\div 5", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "35 \\div 5", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "40 \\div 5", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "45 \\div 5", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "36 \\div 6", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "42 \\div 6", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "48 \\div 6", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "54 \\div 6", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "42 \\div 7", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "49 \\div 7", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "56 \\div 7", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "63 \\div 7", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "56 \\div 8", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "64 \\div 8", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "72 \\div 8", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "54 \\div 9", "answer": "6"},
    {"question": "63 \\div 9", "answer": "7"},
    {"question": "72 \\div 9", "answer": "8"},
    {"question": "81 \\div 9", "answer": "9"}
]